Eloise Hubbard Linscott collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series II: Sound Recordings
  - SR038, September 27, 1947, 1 10-inch disc
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr038b
      - Benjamin Dean (fragment)
  - SR039, November 16, 1941, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by George (Rocky Mountain George) Brown, in Tamworth, New Hampshire.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr039a
      - Long-Waisted Peggy
      - John Hopper's Hill
      - The Jam on Gerry's Rocks
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr039b
      - The Robber Song
  - SR040, September 27, 1946, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Alice Robie, in Pittsburg, New Hampshire. Collector's original ID: III. See SR043 for the first part of "The Battle of Fredericksburg."
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr040a
      - Battle of Fredericksburg (continued)
      - Margaret Gray
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr040b
      - Joe Bowers (fragment)
      - Down by the Old Oak Tree (Squire Macauley)
  - SR041, September 27, 1946, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Alice Robie, in Pittsburg, New Hampshire. Collector's original ID: IV.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr041a
      - Strong Bow (story of an Indian boy)
      - Gay Gold Chain [Plain Gold Chain]
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr041b
      - Silver Dagger (Drowsy Sleeper)
  - SR042, September 27, 1946, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Alice Robie, in Pittsburg, New Hampshire. "Pat O'Brien" continues on SR043, Side A. Collector's original ID: I.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr042a
      - Bold Prince of Royals
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr042b
      - Pat O'Brien
  - SR043, September 27, 1946, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Alice Robie, in Pittsburg, New Hampshire. See SR040, Side A, for the continuation of "The Battle of Fredericksburg." Collector's original ID: II.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr043a
      - Pat O'Brien (continued)
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr043b
      - Foggy Dew (fragment)
      - Lass of Mohea (fragment)
      - The Battle of Fredericksburg
  - SR044, August 29, 1946, 1 10-inch disc
    On Side A: "The Swallow" is performed by an unidentified pianist. Side B: "Whaling song" performed by Bert Richardson. "Sprig of Shilleleah and Shamrock So Green" performed by Harry A. Simpson. "Blow, Boys, Blow" performed by Dick Richardson. "Shillelah" is an alternate spelling of "Shilleleah." The person heard giggling at breaks in "Blow, Boys, Blow" is almost certainly Linscott.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr044a
      - Whaling song
      - Sprig of Shilleleah and Shamrock So Green
      - The Swallow (Herondelle)
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr044b
      - Blow, Boys, Blow
  - SR045, August 29, 1946, 1 10-inch disc
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr045a
      - Burial At Sea (A Sailor's Grave)
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr045b
      - Testing (whistling)
      - I Am Lonely Tonight
      - Sweet Sixteen
  - SR046, 1944 or before, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Captain Charlton Lyman Smith, in Marblehead, Massachusetts, during or before 1944 (the year he died). Collector's original ID: XVIII.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr046a
      - A-Roving [Amsterdam; Maid of Amsterdam]
      - Blow the Man Down
      - Sally Brown
      - Whisky Johnny
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr046b
      - Haul Away, Joe
      - Renzo [Reuben Ranzo]
  - SR047, 1944 or before, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Captain Charlton Lyman Smith, in Marblehead, Massachusetts, during or before 1944 (the year he died). Linscott notes on the disc sleeve that this disc is a duplicate. Collector's original ID: XX.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr047a
      - Haul Away, Joe
      - Renzo [Reuben Ranzo]
      - A Long Time Ago
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr047b
      - Amsterdam [A-Roving; Maid of Amsterdam]
      - Blow the Man Down
      - Sally Brown
      - Whisky Johnny
  - SR048, undated, 1 10-inch disc
    Chet Sargent performed "Billy Boy" and all songs on Side B; his performances are accompanied by guitar. Captain Charlton Lyman Smith performed "A Long Time Ago," in Marblehead, Massachusetts. Eloise Hubbard Linscott performed "My Grandma Lived on Yonder Green" and "Jennie Jenkins." This disc is a compilation of other recordings in the collection. Collector's original ID: XIX.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr048a
      - Billy Boy
      - My Grandma Lived on Yonder Green
      - A Long Time Ago
      - Jennie Jenkins
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr048b
      - Amsterdam (fragment) [Maid of Amsterdam]
      - Canaday I-O (fragment)
      - Tittery Nan
  - SR049, November 11, 1941, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Charles (Uncle Charlie) Ronco, in Dover-Foxcroft, Maine. Both"Rossignol Sauvage" and its continuation sung in French.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr049a
      - Rossignol Sauvage
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr049b
      - Rossignol Sauvage (continued)
  - SR050, November 11, 1941, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Charles (Uncle Charlie) Ronco, in Dover-Foxcroft, Maine. "Second Rossignol Sauvage" sung in French.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr050a
      - Second Rossignol Sauvage (Sparrow Song)
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr050b
      - Late Evening Dew
  - SR051, February 1942, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by David M. (Dave) Swett, of Framingham, Massachusetts. It is not clear if the recording was made there. Side B is blank.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr051a
      - French Jig
      - Unidentified reel
  - SR052, May 31, 1951, 1 10-inch disc
    While the notes on the disc sleeve indicate that Dave Swett played fiddle on "Waltz of the Bells," it is not apparent from the recordings that this is a fiddle tune. Also, the recording on Side B are noted as made in Lebanon, New Hampshire. It is not clear from Linscott's notes on disc sleeves if there is one Dave Swett or two--there was a David Swett who lived in Framingham, Massachusetts, and a David Swett who lived in Lebanon, New Hampshire.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr052a
      - Hull's Victory
      - My Heart Sighs
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr052b
      - Waltz of the Bells
      - Waltz of the Bells (continued)
  - SR053, March 31, 1951 (Side A); circa 1943-1953 (Side B), 1 10-inch disc
    Side A recorded in Lebanon, New Hampshire. Side B features Bud Clayton (disc jockey).
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr053a
      - Grand March
      - The Field Artillery Song
      - Anchors Aweigh
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr053b
      - Disc jockey introduces a song
      - No Other Love
  - SR054, circa 1941-1946, 1 10-inch disc
    Side A: Callers are Joy Walker, Gale Clifford, and Walter King. Side B: Walter King is the caller.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr054a
      - Red River Valley
      - My Little Girl
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr054b
      - Untitled
  - SR055, August 8, 1948, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Milton Appleby (fiddle) and Mrs. Milton Appleby (piano), in Gonic, New Hampshire. Collector's original ID: V.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr055a
      - Old French [Rambler's Hornpipe]
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr055b
      - Old Dan Tucker
  - SR056, August 8, 1940 (Side A); September 11, 1940 (Side B), 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by The Singing Smiths.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr056a
      - Gypsy Sweetheart
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr056b
      - Boston Fancy
      - Old Zip Coon
      - Golden Slippers
  - SR057, circa 1943-1953, 1 10-inch disc
    Side B: An unidentified man (possibly Gene Head) performed a spoken word test; Linscott's voice can be heard in the background. Side A is blank.
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr057b
      - Testing
      - Piano solo
      - Chopsticks
  - SR058, March 31, 1951, 1 10-inch disc
    Side A: Performed by David Mann (the caller). Side B: Performed by Harry Dennis (the caller). Disc recorded in Lebanon, New Hampshire.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr058a
      - Going to Boston
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr058b
      - 4H Closer (continued)
  - SR059, April 2, 1951, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Val Hardy, in Enfield, New Hampshire. Collector's original ID: II.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr059a
      - Money Musk [Monymusk]
      - Arkansas Traveler
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr059b
      - Pop Goes the Weasel
  - SR060, April 2, 1951, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Val Hardy, in Enfield, New Hampshire. Collector's original ID: III.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr060a
      - Lamplighter's Hornpipe
      - Wild Goose Chase
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr060b
      - Unidentified schottische
      - Speed the Plow [Speed the Plough]
  - SR061, October 28, 1945, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Arthur W. Hanson (spoken introductions and fiddle), in Ossipee, New Hampshire. Collector's original ID: II.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr061a
      - Mountain Hornpipe (Pig Town Fling)
      - Paddy on the Railroad
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr061b
      - Little Judy's Reel [Lil Judy's Reel]
      - St. Anne's Reel
      - Come Haste to the Wedding [Haste to the Wedding]
  - SR062, October 27, 1945, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Arthur W. Hanson (spoken introductions and fiddle), in Ossipee, New Hampshire. Collector's original ID: I.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr062a
      - Tuning
      - Turkey in the Straw
      - Irish Washerwoman
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr062b
      - Liverpool Hornpipe
      - Durang's Hornpipe
      - Lamplighter's Hornpipe
  - SR063, March 19, 1941 (Side A); circa 1940-1941 (Side B), 1 10-inch disc
    Side A: Performed by Mrs. Harold W. Pritchard (Margaret). While a location isn't noted on the disc sleeve, Harold and Margaret Pritchard lived in Newbury, Massachusetts in 1940. Side B: Performed by Mrs. Roy Cushman.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr063a
      - Damon and Phyllis
      - Sailing in a Boat
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr063b
      - Little Match Girl
      - There Was An Old Man, Lived Under the Hill (fragments)
  - SR064, circa 1943-1953, 1 10-inch disc
    Side A: "Oxen Song (fragment)" performed by Sam Young, Sr., in North Anson, Maine "Mrs. Murphy's Little Dog" performed by Smith Paine (fiddle), in Wolfeboro, New Hampshire. Side B: Songs performed by unidentified women.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr064a
      - Oxen Song (fragment)
      - Mrs. Murphy's Little Dog [Mrs. Murphy's Lil Dog]
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr064b
      - You Tell Me Your Dream, I'll Tell You Mine
      - If I Had My Way (solo)
      - If I Had My Way (duet)
  - SR065, April 12, 1940, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by the 2nd- and 3rd-grade students of Dedham Country Day School, with piano accompaniment, in Dedham, Massachusetts. Collector's original ID: III.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr065a
      - Billy Boy
      - Monkey's Wedding
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr065b
      - All Bound Round with a Woolen String
      - A Bear Went Over the Mountain
      - Bingo
  - SR066, October 28, 1945, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Arthur W. Hanson (fiddle and calls), in Ossipee, New Hampshire. Collector's original ID: III.
    - Side A: Music and calls for the dance Boston Fancy, afc1942002_sr066a
      - Soldier's Joy
      - Sicilian Circle (tune: Larry O'Gaff)
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr066b
      - Sicilian Circle (tune: Larry O'Gaff) (continued)
      - Jennie Lind Polka [Jenny Lind Polka]
      - Girl With the Blue Dress On
  - SR067, September 24, 1946, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Mrs. Lois A. Comstock, in Clarksville, New Hampshire. Side B is blank. Collector's original ID: I.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr067a
      - Fair Charlotte
      - Fair Charlotte
  - SR068, September 27, 1946, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Abraham (Abe) Washburn, in Kidderville, New Hampshire. Side B is blank. Collector's original ID: III.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr068a
      - Danny Sullivan
  - SR069, September 28, 1946, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Maynard Reynolds, in Pittsburg, New Hampshire. Collector's original ID: III.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr069a
      - All Of Her Answers It Was No
      - Yorkla Harlin
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr069b
      - Ramsgate
      - The Oak and the Ash
      - Harley-Ay-Little Lay-O
      - Soldier Boy
  - SR070, circa September 28, 1946, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Sid Luther, in Colebrook, New Hampshire. Linscott indicates Side A as "testing." The date is conjectural, based on the date given for SR073 and SR278. Collector's original ID: II.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr070a
      - Whiskey, You're the Devil
      - Johnny's Gone for a Soldier
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr070b
      - Chippewa Stream
  - SR071, circa September 28, 1946, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Sid Luther, in Colebrook, New Hampshire. The date is conjectural, based on the date given for SR073 and SR278. "Edwin Merry" is a variant of the tune for "Dark British Foes." Collector's original ID: III.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr071a
      - Girl from Pittsburg
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr071b
      - Edwin Merry (Part 1)
  - SR072, circa September 28, 1946, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Sid Luther, in Colebrook, New Hampshire. The date is conjectural, based on the date given for SR073 and SR278. "Edwin Merry" is a variant of the tune for "Dark British Foes." Collector's original ID: IV.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr072a
      - Edwin Merry
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr072b
      - Edwin Merry
  - SR073, September 28, 1946, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Sid Luther, in Colebrook, New Hampshire. Collector's original ID: V.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr073a
      - George Riley
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr073b
      - George Riley (continued)
      - Charming Sally Ann
  - SR074, undated
    Performed by Sid Luther, in Colebrook, New Hampshire. Side B is blank. The date is conjectural, based on the date given for SR073 and SR278. Collector's original ID: VI.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr074a
      - Fanny More [Fanny Moore]
      - Give My Love To Mother
  - SR075, September 26, 1947, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Eugene (Gene) Andrews (fiddle), in Norway, Maine. Piano accompaniment by an unknown person. Collector's original ID: I.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr075a
      - Durang's Hornpipe
      - Chorus Jig
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr075b
      - Boston Fancy
      - Miss Brown's Reel
      - Larry O'Gaff
      - Test
  - SR076, 1951, 1 10-inch disc
    The first song performed by an unidentified female singer. "Rose, Rose I Love You " was originally recorded by Frankie Laine but this is a different version, and may not be him. Side B is blank.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr076a
      - Untitled
      - Rose, Rose I Love You
  - SR077, January 20, 1953, 1 10-inch disc
    Recorded from a radio broadcast. Dwight D. (Dwight David) Eisenhower is the speaker. The recording on Side A begins after the address had begun. Side B continues the address, with a brief gap of a few words at the beginning. The recording on Side B ends before the address is concluded.
    - Side A: First Inauguration of Dwight D. Eisenhower, afc1942002_sr077a
      - The Inaugural Address (Part 3)
    - Side B: First Inauguration of Dwight D. Eisenhower, afc1942002_sr077b
      - The Inaugural Address (Part 4)
  - SR078, January 20, 1953, 1 10-inch disc
    Recorded from a radio broadcast. Invocation given by Patrick O'Boyle, Archbishop of Washington. An unidentified announcer narrates events during the inauguration.
    - Side A: First Inauguration of Dwight D. Eisenhower, afc1942002_sr078a
      - Hail to the Chief
      - Stars and Stripes Forever
    - Side B: First Inauguration of Dwight D. Eisenhower, afc1942002_sr078b
      - Stars and Stripes Forever
      - Invocation
  - SR079, January 20, 1953, 1 10-inch disc
    Recorded from a radio broadcast. Dorothy Maynor sings "The Star Spangled Banner." Speakers include Eugene Conley and Richard M. (Milhous) Nixon. Collector's original ID: 2.
    - Side A: First Inauguration of Dwight D. Eisenhower, afc1942002_sr079a
      - Star Spangled Banner
      - Richard M. Nixon Takes the Oath of Office as Vice President
    - Side B: First Inauguration of Dwight D. Eisenhower, afc1942002_sr079b
      - America, the Beautiful
  - SR080, January 20, 1953, 1 10-inch disc
    Recorded from a radio broadcast. Dwight D. (Dwight David) Eisenhower is the speaker. An unidentified announcer narrates events during the inauguration. Side B: The address continues, with a brief gap of a few words at the beginning. The recording ends before the address is concluded. Collector's original ID: 3.
    - Side A: First Inauguration of Dwight D. Eisenhower, afc1942002_sr080a
      - Eisenhower Takes the Oath of Office
      - The Inaugural Address (Part 1)
    - Side B: First Inauguration of Dwight D. Eisenhower, afc1942002_sr080b
      - The Inaugural Address
  - SR081, September 26, 1947, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Eugene (Gene) Andrews (fiddle and jew's harp), in Norway, Maine.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr081a
      - Jenny Lind Polka [Jennie Lind Polka]
      - Five Step Schottische
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr081b
      - Untitled Hornpipe
      - Arkansas Traveler
      - Turkey in the Straw
  - SR082, undated, 1 10-inch disc
    Approximately the first 40 seconds of Side A is blank; the rest is an unidentified male singer. Side B is blank.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr082a
      - Testing
  - SR083, 1 10-inch disc
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr083a
      - S Wonderful
      - Untitled
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr083b
      - Untitled
  - SR084, circa 1948-1949, 1 6.5-inch disc
    Performers include Gene (probably Gene Head) and Al Miller. Both Sides A and B include readings from texts. Side B: A portion was recorded in Wolfeboro, New Hampshire. Another portion may have been recorded (in part) from a radio broadcast.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr084a
      - Testing
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr084b
      - Testing
  - SR085, October 27, 1945, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Lillian (Mrs. George) Beacham, in Wolfeboro, New Hampshire.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr085a
      - Chickadee
      - Old Dan Tucker
      - Billy Boy
      - Grandma's Old Arm Chair (fragment) [Grandmother's Arm Chair]
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr085b
      - Grandmother's Arm Chair [Grandma's Old Arm Chair]
      - Rhinosceros Song
  - SR086, May 14, 1949 (Side A); circa 1943-1953 (Side B), 1 10-inch disc
    Performers include the Bourne Male Quartet and Chorus. Side B: Includes piano accompaniment. Songs 2 and 3 are duets with female voices.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr086a
      - Ryo Grande (solo and chorus) [Rio Grande]
    - Side B: Testing, afc1942002_sr085b
      - On Top of Old Smokey
      - Foggy Dew
  - SR087, September 17, 1944, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Lena Bourne Fish, in East Jaffrey, New Hampshire. Collector's original ID: I.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr087a
      - Bill the Weaver
      - Jolly Roving Tar
      - Barbara Allen
    - Side B: Testing, afc1942002_sr087b
      - The Jolly Tinker
      - Crazy Jane
  - SR088, April 19, 1951, 1 10-inch disc
    Recorded from a radio broadcast. Speakers include Douglas MacArthur. Introduction by Sam Rayburn. Collector's original ID: I.
    - Side A: Douglas MacArthur's Farewell Address before the U.S. Congress (Part 1), afc1942002_sr088a
    - Side B: Douglas MacArthur's Farewell Address before the U.S. Congress (Part 2), afc1942002_sr088b
  - SR089, April 19, 1951, 1 10-inch disc
    Recorded from a radio broadcast. Speakers include Douglas MacArthur. Collector's original ID: II.
    - Side A: Douglas MacArthur's Farewell Address before the U.S. Congress (Part 3), afc1942002_sr089a
    - Side B: Douglas MacArthur's Farewell Address before the U.S. Congress (Part 4), afc1942002_sr089b
  - SR090, April 19, 1951, 1 10-inch disc
    Recorded from a radio broadcast. Speakers include Douglas MacArthur. Collector's original ID: III.
    - Side A: Douglas MacArthur's Farewell Address before the U.S. Congress (Part 5), afc1942002_sr090a
    - Side B: Douglas MacArthur's Farewell Address before the U.S. Congress (Part 6), afc1942002_sr090b
  - SR091, April 19, 1951, 1 10-inch disc
    Recorded from a radio broadcast. Speakers include Douglas MacArthur. Collector's original ID: IV.
    - Side A: Douglas MacArthur's Farewell Address before the U.S. Congress (Part 7), afc1942002_sr091a
    - Side B: Douglas MacArthur's Farewell Address before the U.S. Congress (Part 8), afc1942002_sr091b
  - SR092, April 19, 1951, 1 10-inch disc
    Recorded from a radio broadcast. Speakers include Douglas MacArthur. Collector's original ID: V.
    - Side A: Douglas MacArthur's Farewell Address before the U.S. Congress (Part 9), afc1942002_sr092a
    - Side B: Douglas MacArthur's Farewell Address before the U.S. Congress (Part 10), afc1942002_sr092b
  - SR093, April 19, 1951, 1 10-inch disc
    Recorded from a radio broadcast. Speakers include Douglas MacArthur and Sam Rayburn. Collector's original ID: VI.
    - Side A: Announcement following Douglas MacArthur's Farewell Address before the U.S. Congress, afc1942002_sr093a
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr093b
      - Stars and Stripes Forever
  - SR094, May 17, 1950, 1 12-inch disc
    Performed by the Bourne Male Quartet and Chorus. Side B: "OK, Frank" can be heard at the very end of the recording. Collector's original IDs: 1 (Side A) and 2 (Side B). The date is conjectural based on this recording coming from the same session when SR095-098 were recorded.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr094a
      - Rio Grande [Ryo Grande]
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr094b
      - Blow the Man Down
  - SR095, May 17, 1950, 1 12-inch disc
    Performed by the Bourne Male Quartet and Chorus, and William J. (Jack) Sherrard. Collector's original IDs: 7 (Side A) and 8 (Side B).
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr095a
      - Homeward Bound
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr095b
      - Johnny's Gone to Hilo [Tommy's Gone to Hilo]
  - SR096, May 17, 1950, 1 12-inch disc
    Performed by the Bourne Male Quartet and Chorus; Cox is the soloist. Collector's original IDs: 3 (Side A) and 4 (Side B); SR098 has the same numbers. The date is conjectural based on this recording coming from the same session when SR094-095 and SR097-098 were recorded.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr096a
      - A Long Time Ago
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr096b
      - Blow, Boys, Blow
  - SR097, May 17, 1950, 1 12-inch disc
    Performed by the Bourne Male Quartet and Chorus. Side A: Riddell is the soloist. Side B: Cox is the soloist. William J. (Jack) Sherrard may have performed a solo on one of these recordings. Collector's original IDs: 7 (Side A) and 8 (Side B). The date is conjectural based on this recording coming from the same session when SR094-096 and SR098 were recorded.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr097a
      - Homeward Bound
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr097b
      - Johnny's Gone to Hilo [Tommy's Gone to Hilo]
  - SR098, May 17, 1950, 1 12-inch disc
    Performed by the Bourne Male Quartet and Chorus, and William J. (Jack) Sherrard. Collector's original IDs: 3 (Side A) and 4 (Side B); SR096 has the same numbers. The date is conjectural based on this recording coming from the same session when SR094-097 were recorded.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr098a
      - A Long Time Ago
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr098b
      - Blow, Boys, Blow
  - SR099, circa 1940-1941, 1 12-inch disc (broken)
    Side A: Linscott's voice, and that of an unidentified man, can be heard in the last 30 seconds. Side B: Linscott speaks at the beginning of the recording. "Bill" is identified as the performer.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr099a
      - Piano solo
      - Testing
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr099b
      - Testing
      - Home on the Range
      - Female vocal selection
      - Testing
      - Unidentified orchestra selection
  - SR100, circa 1940-1941, 1 12-inch disc (broken)
    Performed by Arthur Treadwell Walden, of Tamworth, New Hampshire. Collector's original ID: E5.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr100a
      - I Strung My Dogs in the Gloaming
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr100b
      - Dog Puncher's Song
  - SR101, circa 1939-1941, 1 12-inch disc
    Performed by Edson H. Cole (fiddle and vocals), in Freedom, New Hampshire. Collector's original ID: 3 (Side A); 4 (Side B)